Guide to the Mark D. Weiser Papers, 1969-1999
Department of Special Collections
- Series 4. Patents / Intellectual Property files
  - Interactive contents revealing storage device Patent no. 5,530,235 1996 June 25 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Electronic book Patent no. 5,534,888 1996 July 9 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - System for granting ownership of device by user based on requested level of ownership, present state of the device, and the context of the device Patent no. 5,544,321 1996 Aug. 6 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Wiping metaphor as a user interface for operating on graphical objects on an interactive graphical display Patent no. 5,548,705 1996 Aug. 20 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Method for granting a user request .... Patent no. 5,555,376 1996 Sept. 10 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Method for triggering selected machine event .... Patent no. 5,603,054 1997 Feb. 11 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Method for selectively performing event on computer controlled device .... Patent no. 5,611,050 1997 Mar. 11 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Event consistent graphical user interface on a high communication latency mobile computer, 1995 June 7 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - One button searching of long lists Patent no. 5,786,819, 1998 July 28 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Patents: Transferring data from a portable computer "DocuWatch" LI/94037 R/94007 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Patents: Recording and retrieval of information relevant to the activities of a user "FMN threads model" LI/93004 R/93013 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Patents: Transferring data from a portable computer R/94007 GB (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Patents: Memorandum: Invention proposal: LI/093013/IRG (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Patents: PCT World Intellectual Property Organization International Patent Classification: HOYN 7/00, G04G 1/00, G06F 15/02 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - NASA-PARC memo of understanding, 1997 Feb. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - NDA to Microsoft, 1998 Oct. 2 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - NDA/CDA approvals (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Confidential Disclosure Agreements - Legal has originals (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Confidential Disclosure Agreements - instructions (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Confidential Disclosure Agreements - individual forms (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Confidential Disclosure Agreements - contractor forms (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Patents/Applications for Minder [1 of 3] (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Patents/Applications for Minder [2 of 3] (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Patents/Applications for Minder [3 of 3] (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Patent information: Foreign filings (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Patent information: Fuji Xerox (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Franklin Elect: Patent information/status, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - PDReader/PARC meeting, 1998 Mar. 10 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - PDReader Workshop, 1997 June 5 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - PDReader Marketing requirements document (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Permission release forms (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - PARC video card [1 of 3] (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - PARC video card [2 of 3] (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - PARC video card [3 of 3] (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Patents [1 of 10] (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Patents [2 of 10] (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Patents [3 of 10] (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Patents [4 of 10] (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Patents [5 of 10] (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Patents [6 of 10] (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Patents [7 of 10] (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Patents [8 of 10] (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Patents [9 of 10] (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Patents [10 of 10] (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Stanford License agreement (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - University of Maryland - software license agreement (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - University of Maryland - patent policy (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - United States patent (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - United States patent (doubles) [1 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - United States patent (doubles) [2 of 2] (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Series 5. Subject files
  This series contains reports, correspondence, notes, product literature, and other documents kept by Mark Weiser on a variety of subjects, including other notable figures and companies in the computer industry.
  - Abstract, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - ACM [Association of Computing Machinery] (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Active Book Company (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Ada Quit (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Administrivia (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - ADS PMC [Architecture & Document Services / Patent Management Committee] meeting RU2507, 1999 Apr. 1 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - ADS PMC [Architecture & Document Services / Patent Management Committee] meeting, 1999 Apr. 1 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - ADS PMC [Architecture & Document Services / Patent Management Committee] (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - AEA [American Electronics Association] [1 of 4] (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - AEA [American Electronics Association] [2 of 4] (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - AEA [American Electronics Association] [3 of 4] (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - AEA [American Electronics Association] [4 of 4] (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Agreements (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Allaire remarks to meeting of Research Board, 1987 Mar. 4 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - American Electronics Assocation (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - AOD (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Apple Patent (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - ARPA Contracts / proposals, abstracts [1 of 2] (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - ARPA Contracts / proposals, abstracts [2 of 2] (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - ARPA Contracts / proposals - Infrastructure for Ubiquitous Computing contract (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - ARPA Contracts / proposals - Low-power S/W proposal abstract (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - ARPA - general (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - ARPA - patent regulations (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - ARPA proposal abstract - Infrastructure for Ubiquitous National Information Enterprise (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - ARPA reports [1 of 11] (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - ARPA reports [2 of 11] (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - ARPA reports [3 of 11] (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - ARPA reports [4 of 11] (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - ARPA reports [5 of 11] (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - ARPA reports [6 of 11] (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - ARPA reports [7 of 11] (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - ARPA reports [8 of 11] (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - ARPA reports [9 of 11] (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - ARPA reports [10 of 11] (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - ARPA reports [11 of 11] (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - ARPA research program in national-scale information enterprises (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - ARPA semi-annual reports (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - ARPA semi-annual report - Infrastructure for Ubiquitous Computing, 1993 Jan. 6 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - ARPA Technology Reinvestment project (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - ARPA timecard procedures (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - ARPA - wireless / low-power PI meeting (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Low-power software ARPA proposal (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Infrastructure for Ubiquitous National Information Enterprise / ARPA proposal [1 of 2] (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Infrastructure for Ubiquitous National Information Enterprise / ARPA proposal [2 of 2] (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Situated user interfalls for mobile information systems / ARPA proposals (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - ARPA proposals: Wireless, adaptive, & mobile information systems (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Asian entrepreneurs, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - ATM [Asynchronous Transfer Model] (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Attendee list [1 of 5] (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Attendee list [2 of 5] (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Attendee list [3 of 5] (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Attendee list [4 of 5] (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Attendee list [5 of 5] (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Attorneys: Gray, Cary, Ware & Freiderich (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Attorneys: Gunderson, Dettmer, Stough, Villeneuve, Franklin, & Hachigian (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Attorneys: Venture Law Group (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Australia (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Award statistics at PARC, 1996 - 1998 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Baby Dragon (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Badian / DARPA [1 of 2] (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Badian / DARPA [2 of 2] (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Baras collaboration (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Berkeley new materials (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Berkeley retreat, 1991 Jan. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Bert's ideas on research - Sun Microsystems Laboratories, Inc. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Bessemer Venture Partners (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Biographical information: Vita, 1996 Feb. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Biographical information: Mark's bio (new) (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Biographical information: Mark's business cards (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Blue ribbon panel - Executive Office of the President Office of Management & Budget (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Blueprint to the digital economy (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Bluetooth Adoptors Agreement form, 1998 May 5 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - BMW, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - BMW personal travel assistant (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Book project (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Borg, Anita (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Borg, Anita - press - articles (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Press release re: Anita Borg (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Borg, Anita - CRA - Grace Hopper (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Borg, Anita (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Borg, Anita - National Academy of Engineers letter, 1998 Feb. 2 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Borg, Anita / IRL (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Borg, Anita - The Institute for Women and Technology (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Budget, 1995 - 2000 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Budget - Capital 3724, 1997 Oct. (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Budget: OCT / RED / UER [1 of 2], 1999 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Budget: OCT / RED / UER [2 of 2], 1999 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Building a leadership position in the Electronic Document Environment (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Burlap status review, 1998 Apr. (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Business contacts (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Business inquiries - Alps [1 of 3] (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Business inquiries - Alps [2 of 3] (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Business inquiries - Alps [3 of 3] (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Business reference (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - CACM paper [1 of 2], 1993 July (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - CACM paper [2 of 2], 1993 July (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - California housing (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Campbell, Burke (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Candidates - recommendations (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Canon Hi-Tech Exhibition - C. Mudge trip report (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Cancer Support and Education Center (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Cardoza, David E. (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - CDI [Contemporary Design Issues] (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - CDR [Creative Document Research] (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Cedar Source code (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - CEMA (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - CESDIS - annual report - Year 9, 1996 July - 1997 June (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Cerberus (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Changeology (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Charts [1 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Charts [2 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Chicago show notes (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Childcare (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - CIC Committee (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Cioch (Kaplan) (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - CMU dual use consortium (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - CNRI (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Columbia Center for Telecommunications Research (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - COMDEX [1 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - COMDEX [2 of 2] (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - CompCon, 1994 Spring (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Computer Magazine (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Computer Magazine - article peer review (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Computer Museum (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Computer Science and Telecommunications Board, National Research Council (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - CRA [Computing Research Association] (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Computing Research Association by-laws (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Computing Research Association membership dues (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Computing Research Association, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Computing Research Association [1 of 3], 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Computing Research Association [2 of 3], 1992 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Computing Research Association [3 of 3], 1992 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Computing Research Association [1 of 6], 1993 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Computing Research Association [2 of 6], 1993 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Computing Research Association [3 of 6], 1993 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Computing Research Association [4 of 6], 1993 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Computing Research Association [5 of 6], 1993 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Computing Research Association [6 of 6], 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Computing Research Association, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Computing Research Association - Grace Hopper celebration [1 of 2] (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Computing Research Association - Grace Hopper celebration [2 of 2] (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - CRA [Computing Research Association] (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - CRA [Computing Research Association] (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - CRA [Computing Research Association] - Board of Directors list (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - CRA [Computing Research Association] - Board of Directors meeting, 1993 Dec. 9 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - CRA [Computing Research Association] - Industrial & affiliate members (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - CRA [Computing Research Association] survey prelims, 1993 Dec. 5 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Conference lists (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Conference resources (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Consulting agreements (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Consumer Electronic Manufacturing Association / Electronics Industry Association (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Contributions (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Conversation with John Seely Brown and notes from project meetings (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - CPSR (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - CR&T (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - CR&T Women's Council (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] [1 of 2] (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] [2 of 2] (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] overview slides - Mudge (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] vision meeting [1 of 4], 1988 Nov. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] vision meeting [2 of 4], 1988 Nov. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] vision meeting [3 of 4], 1988 Nov. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] vision meeting [4 of 4], 1988 Nov. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] off-site meeting, 1988 Nov. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] off-site meeting: readings, 1988 Nov. 17-19 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] records (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] report / John Hughes (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] research in programming languages and systems [1 of 2], 1976 - 1979 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] research in programming languages and systems [2 of 2], 1976 - 1979 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] retreat, 1994 Nov. 10 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] retreat, 1994 Nov. 17 - 18 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] retreat, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] retreat, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] support staff retreat: workbook, 1991 Aug. 28 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - CSL [Computer Science Laboratory] support staff retreat: workbook and pre-reading, 1992 Sept. 22 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - CSNS, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - CSNS: budget, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - CSTB [Computer Science & Telecommunications Board] (NRC) (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Curriculum vita - published articles - Mark Weiser, 1996 Feb. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Customer visit program (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Dart and Xerox memorandum of understanding, 1999 Feb. 15 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Data and Strategies Group (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - DataGlyphs - automated document factory (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Defense Technology Commercialization - David Trollman (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Discussion about creating a sabbatical system at PARC (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - DocuCard, 1994 Dec. 22 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Document Futures board (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Document solutions company - XEROX, 1996 Nov. 21-22 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - DocuWorld - Brazil, 1998 May (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Domingo, Rich - meeting [1 of 2] (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Domingo, Rich - meeting [2 of 2] (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Drafts (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - DSA, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Pre-reading for DSA review, n.d. Mar 4 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - EDSF [Electronic Document Systems Foundation] Advisory Board (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - EDT Council (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Edison Welding Institute [1 of 8] (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Edison Welding Institute [2 of 8] (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Edison Welding Institute [3 of 8] (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Edison Welding Institute [4 of 8] (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Edison Welding Institute [5 of 8] (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Edison Welding Institute [6 of 8] (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Edison Welding Institute [7 of 8] (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Edison Welding Institute [8 of 8] (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Editor data [1 of 4] (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Editor data [2 of 4] (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Editor data [3 of 4] (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Editor data [4 of 4] (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Editor experiment (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Embodied interaction: Exploring the foundations of a new approach to HCI (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Employee evaluation, 1973 May 30 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Employee satisfaction measurement system for Alan Demers, 1993 Sept. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Employee satisfaction measurement system for Dan Greene, 1993 Sept. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Employee satisfaction measurement system for Mark Weiser, 1994 Nov. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Endeavor Expedition Project, U.C. Berkeley, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Environmental Architecture (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Etchieson, Diane - resume (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Ethnography (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - EuroPARC (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Fellows - confidential (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Focus Group: Focus Group info (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Focus Group: Nichols Research, Inc., 1996 Oct. 10 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Focus Group: Nichols Research, Inc.: respondent profile list (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Focus Group: user questions (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Franklin Electronic Publishing (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Franklin Electronic Publishing (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - FujiXerox - XC-FX Communications matrix (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - FujiXerox [1 of 2] (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - FujiXerox [2 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Gallaire, Herve - Architecture and Document Services Technology Center (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Garden light meter (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Gartner Group (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Gates, Bill. Comdex '94 speech re: Mobile Computing [transparency], 1994 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - General Magic (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Giga Research (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Global Village Communication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Glyphs - reprints glyph technology for hardcopy digital documents [1 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Glyphs - reprints glyph technology for hardcopy digital documents [2 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Glyphs - reprints New York Times article (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Gold, Rich (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Graduation - Computer Science (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Harrison, Beverly L. (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Harvard Business School (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - HCS software specifications (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Headhunters (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Heidelberg-Helmut Kipphan visit, 1999 Feb. 1 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Hewlett Packard [1 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Hewlett Packard [2 of 2] (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Hewlett Packard Logic state analyzer Model 1601A (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Hewlett Packard Digital multimeter Model 3435A (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Hewlett Packard Power supply Model 6203B (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Hewlett Packard Power supply Model 6214A (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Hikari (Minder) (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - How to write a good systems paper (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Human factors at BT Laboratories (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Hyperacuity (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - ILI [International Leadership Institute] (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Institute for the Future, 1998 Mar. (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Institute for the Future. Board of Trustees, New York City [1 of 2], 1998 June 9-10 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Institute for the Future. Board of Trustees, New York City [2 of 2], 1998 June 9-10 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Institute for the Future. Board of Trustees meeting, 1998 Nov. 3-4 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Institute for the Future. The future of information and communications technology in Asia, 1997 Oct. - 1998 Dec. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Institute for the Future. Sonoma Mission Inn (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Institute for the Future. Sonoma Mission Inn - IFTF meeting, 1999 Mar. 22-23 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - INTEL: INTEL visit, 1994 Nov. 28 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Intellectual property file (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Intelligent devices (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Internet: Xerox sets the standard for the Internet: article / by D. Feinstein (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Internet printing workshop [1 of 2] (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Internet printing workshop [2 of 2] (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Internet Task Force - Electronic commerce (White House paper) (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Internet tuner i-1000 design kit document, v. 1.1. [S.l.]: iReady Group, 1998 July 27 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Inventor awards, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - InXight - reprints - San Jose Mercury News, 1997 Jan. 14 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - InXight - reprints - Information visualization technology (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - IPWG mission statement, 1998 Apr. 1 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - IRL [Institute for Research on Learning] (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - ISAT Travel reimbursement (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - ISAT - completed forms (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - ISAT - expense report forms (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - ISAT - travel requisition forms (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - ISTL / PARC environment, 1996 May 16 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - ITRD [Information Technology Research & Development?], Chapter 5 / Jerry Sheehan. -- draft (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Java license agreement (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Jeremijenko, Natalie H.M. (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Kornfield design (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Krull, Wilhelm (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Lab letters (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - LaserReader (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - LC Technologies, Inc. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Library of Congress. Delivering electronic information in a knowledge-based environment, 1993 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - License agreements: Bell, U.C. Berkeley (UNIX) (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - In memoriam: J.C.R. Licklider, 1915-1990 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Liveboard [1 of 2] (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Liveboard [2 of 2] (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Liveworks, Inc. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Los Alamos National Laboratory (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Lunar Groups: Lunar invoice (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Lunar Designs: [Miscellaneous] (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Management of technology [1 of 3] (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Management of technology [2 of 3] (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Management of technology [3 of 3] (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Management potentials DDS meeting (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Market pricing course M391 Stanford University. A pricing overview. Lecture 1 / Ward Hanson (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Market pricing course M391 Stanford University. Proper role of costs. Lecture 2 / Ward Hanson (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Market pricing course M391 Stanford University. Consumers and prices. Lecture 3 / Ward Hanson (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Market pricing course M391 Stanford University. Estimating price sensitivity. Lecture 4 / Ward Hanson (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Market pricing course M391 Stanford University. Competition. Lecture 5 / Ward Hanson (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Mayfield Fund (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - McColough, C. Peter - speech, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Media (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Media communications [1 of 5] (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Media communications [2 of 5] (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Media communications [3 of 5] (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Media communications [4 of 5] (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Media communications [5 of 5] (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Media contacts, 1996 Aug. 12 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Media space nodes in EDL and CSL (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Meeting agenda, n.d. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Meeting notes, 1999 Feb. 8 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Memberships (Box 40, Folder 16)